Todo
    - DONE Create virtual env
    - DONE Install and setup
    - DONE Init database, super user, test run
    - DONE Create core app for base pages
    - DONE Create app for users
    - DONE Create app for products
        - Add category model
    - DONE List out newest products on the front pages
    - DONE Product detail view
    - DONE category view
    - DONE Add images 
    - DoNE show vendor on product detail
    - DONE vendor detail page
    - DONE Sign up, login, logout
    - DONE Create "my account" page
    - DONE simple search
    - Admin pages for vendors
    - Add product to the cart
    - view cart
    - Checkout
    - implement payment gateway
    - Deploy Project